(Sheldon:)Now, let's talk Aquaman.
(Howard:)What were they thinking,
putting Doctor Octopus's mind
(Howard:)in Spider-Man's body?
(Raj:)Well, I've been quite enjoying that.
(Raj:)It combines all the
superhero fun of Spider-Man
(Raj:)with all the body-switching
shenanigans of Freaky Friday.
(Raj:)original and Lohan.
original and Lohan." You're an idiot.
(Raj:)Hey, what's your problem?
(Howard:)I'm sorry.
I've been kind of snippy lately.
(Howard:)It's probably this stupid diet
I'm on.
(Raj:)-Why are you on a diet?
-I've put on a couple pounds.
(Howard:)Had to buy these pants
in the men's section.
(Raj:)Well, we've all seen your mom.
(Raj:)That Butterball turkey
was bound to come home to roost.
Twelve-hundred dollars!
That's my final offer!
(Stuart:)All right, Sheldon, you win.
(Stuart:)I'm sure Leonard
is gonna love this.
(Sheldon:)Oh, right, a present for Leonard.